{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074672125","data":{"timestamp":" 947074672124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074679909","data":{"timestamp":" 947074679908"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074681489","data":{"timestamp":" 947074681489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074684509","data":{"timestamp":" 947074684509"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074686054","data":{"timestamp":" 947074686054"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074689089","data":{"timestamp":" 947074689088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074690641","data":{"timestamp":" 947074690641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074693284","data":{"timestamp":" 947074693283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074694875","data":{"timestamp":" 947074694875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074699989","data":{"timestamp":" 947074699989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074701549","data":{"timestamp":" 947074701549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074710761","data":{"timestamp":" 947074710761"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074712442","data":{"timestamp":" 947074712442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074716434","data":{"timestamp":" 947074716433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074717992","data":{"timestamp":" 947074717991"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074721627","data":{"timestamp":" 947074721627"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074723196","data":{"timestamp":" 947074723196"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074725547","data":{"timestamp":" 947074725547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074727107","data":{"timestamp":" 947074727107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074731225","data":{"timestamp":" 947074731225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074732804","data":{"timestamp":" 947074732804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074739463","data":{"timestamp":" 947074739463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074739649","data":{"timestamp":" 947074739649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151737"," gameId":" 40985fa0-b2e5-475d-bb1e-f852ea2d6cf4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}